Little Brother
Well, today was a waste of time.
Like every day?
I guess so.
It's like they say: "Life's but a walking shadow, a poor player"!
What does that mean?
No idea.
Doesn't it mean life's pointless?
When I'm at home screaming, "Why am I alive?"
and stuff, my little brother always says that.
Is he trying to cheer you up or not?
Your little brother sounds like a clever kid.
He sure is!
Ken!
Hey!
Hey, c'mon!
Don't just ignore your own flesh-and-blood sister!
Way to disrespect our parents!
I don't believe our parents are relevant here.
Sure they are!
You'll break Mom and Dad's hearts!
Hanako, might he be...
Yep! My little brother Ken!
Isn't he a cutie?
And he's super clever!
I wish I got to have a clever sibling.
Pleased to meet you.
P-Pleased to meet you.
Pl... Pleased to meet you.
What's the matter?
So Kasumi and Olivia exist after all.
Huh? What do you mean?
I thought they might be your imaginary friends.
Mac!
What? That's horrible!
Yep, we really exist.
Your sister's a very good friend to us.
See?
Now then, let's go home together!
What? What's the problem?
We're going to the same place, after all.
Sure, but...
There's a book I want to buy from the bookstore.
Just get Maeda to buy it for you.
You're studying day in, day out.
You should come play outside once in a while!
You're studying day in, day out too.
Yeah, when I have a test the next week!
Hey, I know!
There's a park nearby. Let's go play there before we head home!
Oh, there's a park here?
See? If you don't play, you don't learn anything!
It's pretty empty!
I haven't been to the park in forever.
Same.
We used to play there all the time in elementary school.
Whee!
And then some people will always be a feral child at heart.
Ken! Come join us!
I'll just sit here and read until she says it's time to go home.
What am I even doing here?
Hey.
Look at these. Aren't they beautiful?
Marbles?
Yep. Found them when we were playing in the sandpit.
Look, there's a hole in the table.
Let's use it.
Come on, curve!
Nope, no luck.
Are you good at this kind of thing, Ken?
"Ken-chan"?
Uh, no. I've never done it before.
Well, I'll line them up again, so this time you try.
All right! Let's see what you can do!
What's going on? Whatcha doing?
Wow!
Way to go, Ken!
H-How did you do that?
How?
If you apply horizontal rotational force,
the marble's trajectory will curve.
By analyzing the angle and size of the vectors,
you can derive the path it'll take when you roll it.
Then you adjust the follow-through to apply suitable rotation before the initial propulsion.
O-Oh. I see.
Did you get that, Kasumi?
No, not a bit.
Wow!
I didn't get a word of that,
but it sure was impressive!
It was nothing special.
You should give it a try too, Kasumi!
Can I? Okay then...
I did it!
Wow!
Hanako, look, look!
Ken, time for round two!
Uh... okay.
You try it too, Hanako.
Okay, okay.
I guess playing's...
not all that bad.
You just thought
"Ah, this is heaven on earth", didn'tcha?
I wouldn't go that far.
But I was a tiny bit glad... that I had a big sister.
Just a bit.
Not that I'll admit it.
All right, get ready. Now it's my turn!
My dentures!
Oh my! Dear, what happened?
Say.
How fast can you run 50 meters?
Just over nine seconds.
Do it in five.
To the station.
I guess I was right all along...
She really does ruin everything in the end.
Run for it!
Asobi Asobase.