Armstrong
It all began with a careless remark spoken by their teacher.
Pastimers
Club
Say, which of you is the strongest, do you think?
Me!
Me! Me!
I think that would be me.
They're all nominating themselves.
Aw, come on, there's no way it's either of you two.
I totally can't see either of you beating me.
I'm the strongest here!
You'd be the weakest for sure.
All dainty and delicate.
Though if we're going by looks...
Kasumi's got the biggest rack, so she might be the toughest.
Wha—
Maybe so.
How about I squash you like a bug, then?
A-Actually, I might just be the strongest.
Despite my appearance, I once beat a friend who did pro wrestling in arm wrestling.
Wow, really?
Then let's make it a competition!
The first-ever Pastimer's Club Arm Wrestling Tournament!
You can go first, Teacher.
Bring it on! I'll knock you all out in two seconds flat!
Um, Teacher, when you said
you beat your pro wrestler friend...
I lied.
But why?
I got carried away.
Okay! Opening entertainment's done—
let's get serious now!
First up: me versus Olivia!
On your marks...
Begin!
Oh, it's looking close!
Oh, damn. Olivia's way stronger than I'd thought.
Th-This is about forty percent of my power.
Now I'm gonna... get serious!
H-Here I go...
Oh shit!
Seriously? She's only at forty percent?
If she gets serious, she'll wipe the floor with me!
In that case... I'll use my secret weapon!
"Is this packing tape the extra-adhesive type?"
Honda wins!
Ta-dah!
Um... Hanako... a word?
Did you tell Olivia? Did you tell her about it?
Why, whatever do you mean?
I just made a perfectly banal remark about extra-adhesive packing tape.
Why does that bother you? Don't tell me it relates to your yaoi interests in some way?
Hanako... that's playing dirty!
You made me remember it!
Remember what?
Senpai and the sports shed!
I knew it!
And then
what
happened?
And then what happened?
Next up's Olivia and Kasumi.
Sure.
Oh... Olivia.
You know if you lose to Kasumi,
that makes you the weakest, right?
Damn it! I really, really don't want to lose!
On your marks...
Get set...
Start!
She's pressing her wrist down!
I can see Olivia about to leak ectoplasm!
My, my, Olivia. What a pity.
You're the weakest.
It's not over.
I refuse to die here!
There has to be some way... to turn this around!
Excuse me, Teacher. I wanted to ask about something in English earlier.
Oh, Aozora. Certainly, come in.
Uh... if I'm interrupting, I can come back...
Wait, Aozora!
Kasumi's... about to lose to me.
Give her some encouragement.
Say, "You can do it."
Whisper it... right into her ear.
Give her a shot of energy.
No...
Um... that's quite all right.
Hurry up! If you don't, Kasumi's gonna lose!
Um...
It's really...
Nomura.
You
You can
You can do it.
Bam!
Olivia's the winner!
I win!
That's cheating!
What are you talking about? You should be grateful for that shot of energy.
Hm? Now I'm not sure who's going to win.
I suppose Honda and Nomura are next.
Bring it!
If I can just counter her wrist hold,
I can win this!
And...
begin!
I'mma wristlock you first!
No! No! No! No!
Mommy!
I lost!
M-My arm... it hurts!
She looks like the weakest of the weak.
Um... so how does this work?
I'm impressed you ended up with one win and one loss apiece.
Ah, who cares? I guess we're all even.
That settles that, then.
We settled how sad you are, more like.
What do you mean?
We got a win and a loss each.
Hey, Aozora, how good are you at arm wrestling?
Me? Oh, I'm sure I'm nothing special.
Wanna try?
Sure.
The girls had yet to learn
that the truly strong do not need to boast.